UTU New York State Legislative Board Selected Files 5622
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UTU New York State Legislative Board Selected Files
1962-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Transportation Union (UTU)
5622
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Files.
State legislation files, subject files and case files
5677075
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5711: UTU New York State Legislative Director Files
Railroads--United States.; Railroads -- Employees -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; United Transportation Union; Boardman, Francis B.
5677075
- State Legislation Files (A-Z) and Subject Files (A-Al) (Box 1)
  - Amtrak, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bond Issue, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Boston-Chicago Amtrak Rail Service, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Buffalo Labor Study Program, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Erie-Lackawanna RR, Commuter Service, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Continental Trailways, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Educational Seminar, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Griff Davis, E-L, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Board No. 180, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Health and Welfare Movement, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Health and Welfare Movement, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ICC and Pacific Electric Railway v. Railway Labor Executives Assoc. and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - IRS Form 843, Taxed Pensions (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Implementation of Rail Bond Act, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Insurance, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mass Transportation, 1975-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence of K.R. Moore, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Scope and Contents
    VP of Bus Dept.
  - National Diesel Agreement, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - New York State Occupational Safety and Health Plan, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - RSPO-CRU Briefing Session, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Regional Rail Reorganization Act, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Sale of Property of Bankrupt Railroads, 1975-1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Selective Strike, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Standard of Service For Commuter Railroads, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - State Master Plan for Transportation in New York (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Vandalism, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Wage Movement, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Subway Division, Rochester Transit Corp., 1943-1950 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Adirondack Transit Pine Hills Kingston Merger Attempt, 1964-1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Adirondack Transit Lines, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Merger of Central Greyhound West Ridge and Buffalo and Erie Coach Co., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Berkshire Street Railway, Abandonment of Pittsfield-NY City Rail Service, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Yellow Bus Lines, Limo Service between Pittsfield and NY City, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Transcontinental Lines Inc. and California Long Haul Motor Carriers, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Public Service Coordinated Purchase of Royal Blue Bus Lines, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Penn Central Reorganization, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Packets, Plans, Brochures (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Greyhound's Acquisition of Carey Transit Inc., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Filler Box (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Subject Files (Am-Z) and Case Files (Box 2)
  - Arizona Legislative Board, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Legislative Board, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Colorado Legislative Board, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut Legislative Board, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Florida Legislative Board, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Illinois Legislative Board, 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Indiana Legislative Board, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Kansas Legislative Board, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Maine Legislative Board, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Michigan Legislative Board, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey Legislative Board, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - North Carolina Legislative Board, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ohio Legislative Board, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Oklahoma Legislative Board, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania Legislative Board, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Texas Legislative Board, 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous State Legislative Board Documents, 1963-1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rates of Pay Agreement, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    January 27
  - Alcoholism and Employee Assistance Programs, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)